(Raj:)Oh, well, nice to meet you.
(Isabella:)Nice to meet you, too.
(Isabella:)You know, I have to say,
(Isabella:)based on the candy wrappers
(Isabella:)and the bags
of junk food I see
(Isabella:)in this trash,
I thought the person
(Isabella:)working here was ten years old.
(Raj:)Oh, please, show me
a ten-year-old who knows
(Raj:)to dip Tootsie Rolls in Nutella.
Bueno, um, I'm just going
(Isabella:)to empty your waste paper basket
(Isabella:)and then I'll get
out of your way.
(Raj:)Oh, please, allow me.
(Raj:)That's a lot of empty calories.
(Amy:)Thank you.
(Raj:)You're welcome.
(Isabella:)Okay, uh, okay,
I-I-I have to go.
(Raj:)- Okay.
- Good luck
(Isabella:)with your, um,
space exploration.
(Amy:)Thank you.
(Isabella:)Good luck with your...
future endeavors.
(Sheldon:)Did it work?
(Sheldon:)Are they brain cells yet?
(Amy:)If you'd give me a minute,
I'll tell you.
(Sheldon:)Oh, just let me look.
Oh, my goodness!
(Sheldon:)I see quivering black lines.